betterphoto.com 2019-07-09

# Learn Photography at BetterPhoto.com® - Get to Know Team BetterPhoto!

## About BetterPhoto

This photography site has been guiding online photographers since March 23, 1996. For the first few years, it was called "Graphique"; then we changed our name to BetterPhoto.com. 

### BetterPhoto's Purpose in Life

Our mission is to help you **say "YES!" to your creative dreams**. Read more about BetterPhoto's mission and purpose

### How BetterPhoto Came Into Being

Early in 1996, Jim Miotke, the President and Founder of BetterPhoto.com, got inspired to explore Web publishing, when a friend shared her experiences creating an online college thesis. Seeing the power of online publishing, Jim became inspired, diving whole-heartedly into Web development. He listened to the wisdom: "Write about what you love" and, since he had a passion for photography, Jim published a brief article - his Top Ten Photography Tips on photography. The rest is history. This short article served to launch what was to become the premier educational Web site on photography. 

### BetterPhoto.com Today

  * BetterPhoto offers the best in online photography courses. 
  * BetterPhoto helps photographers share photos with an easy-to-use system that's both affordable and powerful. 
  * BetterPhoto offers fun and inspiration through a strong member community. 
  * BetterPhoto's Deluxe or Pro BetterPholio™ Web site hosting services for photographers is easy-to-use and highly customizable. 
  * BetterPhoto's photo contests are the most fun, objective, and prestigious photography contests on the Web. 
  * BetterPhoto offers two exciting ways to get professional feedback on your photos. 

### Privacy Policy

[Privacy Policy](http://www.iubenda.com/privacy-policy/914415 "Privacy Policy") **Here's more about our high standards on privacy...**  
BetterPhoto.com does not sell our members email addresses or personal information. Never ever ever. All information submitted to BetterPhoto.com is not to be sold or used in any way that violates your right to privacy. Upon registration as a BetterPhoto member, email addresses are collected for the purpose of delivering an optimal experience at BetterPhoto. 

Spam is never endorsed at BetterPhoto.com. Our email newsletters are sent only to those who subscribe on a volunteer, opt-in basis. We also provide numerous opportunities to unsubscribe from these emails, including opt-out links at the bottom of each newsletter. 

BetterPhoto.com does not endorse or tolerate unsolicited sales emails through our automated contact forms. Individuals or companies may not email BetterPhoto members through our contact forms, Q&A, or any BetterPhoto Discussions. When BetterPhoto contacts our own BetterPhoto customer base, it will not be considered unsolicited email. 

BetterPhoto employs cookies to aid us in determining how we can best serve your needs. We use these cookies to track page views, site visitors, referral information, and other statistic data. We also turn to cookies to save items in your shopping cart. We do not use cookies for any illicit purposes. You are free to turn off your cookies when visiting BetterPhoto.com. 

### Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics to collect information about use of this site. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to this site. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve this site. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this site, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this site, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google's ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the [Google Analytics Terms of Use](http://www.google.com/analytics/tos.html) and the [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html). You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this site by [disabling cookies](http://www.usa.gov/optout_instructions.shtml) on your browser.

Google Analytics employs cookies to define user sessions, which allows for the collection of data about how visitors are using the web sites. Google Analytics uses only first-party cookies for data analysis. This means that the cookies are linked to a specific web site domain, and Google Analytics will only use that cookie data for statistical analysis related to your browsing behavior on that specific web site. According to Google, the data collected cannot be altered or retrieved by services from other domains.

If you choose, you can opt out by turning off cookies in the preferences settings in your web browser. For more information on Google Analytics, please visit [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics/)

### Advertising

BetterPhoto may advertise anywhere on our site, but will not advertise on our member's Deluxe or Pro Web sites without their permission. BetterPhoto does not allow intrusive advertising such as pop-ups or pop-unders. Advertising may be found to match specific images, titles, or descriptions. BetterPhoto reserves the right to change advertising on the site at any time. 

### Our Copyright

Unless otherwise noted, photos, graphics, and text - Copyright © Jim Miotke, All Rights Reserved. Some articles are authored by guest contributors and other BetterPhoto staff members; for example, many articles are authored by Denise Miotke and Kerry Drager. No content or photos may be copied or used without written permission from the author or artist who holds copyright of their work. Do not copy other peoples pictures or text without their permission. 

### You Retain Copyright for Your Photos

BetterPhoto Members retain copyright to the photos they upload to BetterPhoto.com. 

### One More Disclaimer

All advice and information provided on this site is intended to help budding photographers find answers to their questions. However, this site and the persons behind it are not to be held accountable, liable, or responsible in any way for this information or how it is used by the individual. 

### Contact Info

_Use theContact Us page to send us a message._

**BetterPhoto Incorporated**  
9909 Manchester Rd, #151.  
Warson Woods MO 63122 

Thank you for your continued support & patronage. Have fun making better photos.
